Brian McLendon II

609-213-3356 / mclendon.brian@gmail.com / teenzombie.com

Graduate of Design with a lifelong passion for the arts and technology. Excellent and diligent with time management, research, and problem solving. Willing and excited by the prospect of learning new skills and perfecting them. Developer of concise print, digital, and interactive media work based on client and coworker input. Growing knowledge of Design, Coding Languages, and User Experiences. Manager of teams and producer of competition winning work. Writer and producer of music and audio associated media since 2003. A regular attendee of art, design, and coding courses in order to expand creative and professional skill sets.

EDUCATION:

2007 - 2009 / Rowan University Bachelor of Arts in Graphic Design

2005 - 2007 / Fashion Institute of Technology Associates in Communication Design

WORK HISTORY:

April 2016 - Present / Franklin Machine Products Graphic Designer and Product Photographer

September 2015 - April 2016 / We Love Photobooths Live Event Technician and Utility

June 2013 - Present / Freelance and Part Time Web, Graphic, and Interactive Design

March 2013 - April 2013 / The Comcast Network Broadcast Graphics | Network Graphics HD Rebuild

October 2011 - February 2012 / G.Girl Illustration | Graphic Design | Pre-Press Setup

February - August 2010 / Village Copier Signage | Advertisement | Pre-Press Setup | Retail Sales | Programming

2008 - 2011 / The Comcast Network Broadcast Graphics | Network Graphics HD rebuild | Live Event Production Utility